Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
I drove out to the orphanage today.
I go every month. remember?
The children are so cute.
If I have a child. maybe I'll raise her
out there in the country.
Show her flowers and trees.
Plus. it's close to Seoul.
The tow truck?
They said it'll take a while.
I love your voice.
It feels romantic
to hear your voice in the snow.
Hold on a moment.
Got a flat tire?
Yes. I called a tow truck.
In this snow.
it could take a while.
Hold on.
Let me take a look.
I said it's okay.
but he's looking at it.
Really?
Just wait for the tow truck.
No. it's not hard
to change a flat tire.
But why bother
when a tow truck's coming?
Hold on a sec.
Status?
Okay. got it.
Hello? Ju-yeon?
I would better get going.
Lock the doors
and just wait for the tow truck.
What?
Hold on.
Love is...
Sweet like...
A mother's...
Tow truck's on its way.
Why does he bother?
Too many people here today.
Sorry to be working
on your birthday again.
I'll be home soon.
Your car's completely sunk.
Thank you. but I'll just wait
for the tow truck.
Thank you.
STUDENT SAFETY VEHICLE
Why isn't he leaving?
Mister...
Wait...
Your skin's so soft.
looks like it'll be easy.
Please don't kill me.
Why not?
I'm...
...pregnant.
Please. let me live.
Dong-su! Dong-su!
- What?
- Come here. quick!
Chief!
Why did you come here?
Stay at home.
We'll keep you posted.
What's going on?
What happened to my daughter?
Don't look!
Nothing's for sure yet.
- Detective Cho!
- What?
What's this?
Move it.
It looks like a head.
Flip it.
Forensics!
Come here. quick!
We found the head!
Look after Chief Jang!
Chief! Sir!
Ju-yeon! Ju-yeon!
Stop taking pictures!
You call yourselves humans?!
Block them off!
At least. heaven helped us.
Otherwise.
we might never have found her.
How ironic.
I was a police detective
for over 30 years...
And I couldn't even protect
my own daughter.
Stop smoking. sir.
I'm sorry.
Really.
I'm so sorry.
To you...
And to Ju-yeon...
I'm so sorry.
Forgive me. Ju-yeon.
I wasn't there for you.
Always late...
Never there when you needed me.
But Ju-yeon...
I promise you this.
I'll make him pay for your pain.
Soo-hyun...
For how long?
There's no rush.
Do you want one or two months off?
All I need is two weeks. sir.
Take more days.
No. I'll see you in two weeks. sir.
That would be good for us...
But are you sure?
Then I'll see to it.
I hope you recover from your grief.
Get some rest.
How could this happen?
Didn't he get engaged
just last month?
I don't believe this.
The capsule is equipped
with GPS and a microphone.
Cool. isn't it?
Good job.
Thanks.
Sure.
Aren't you going back?
Huh?
Anything else to tell me?
No.
Right.
As you know.
I snuck this out.
If something goes wrong.
you and I will...
Don't worry.
Nothing will go wrong.
It looks like the police...
Think these four
are the main suspects.
They've been accused
of similar crimes before.
- Hi. Soo-hyun.
- Hi.
Did you have dinner already?
I would better get going.
I brought some groceries for Dad.
I'll be going then.
Take care. sir.
- You're leaving?
- Yeah.
Shit.
Quiet!
Remember this?
You really don't know?
Fine.
Sir.
What the hell is with him?
He's turning himself in?
Says he killed the girl found
at Bangho Creek two months ago.
And the missing Shinchon girl case
a few years back.
All of a sudden.
he has a conscience?
What the hell? Who did this?
You bastards?
No. sir.
An ambulance came
so I ran up to see.
And this bastard
was practically dying.
What the heck happened?
Well. he didn't say anything yet.
What the hell happened last night?
Help... me... please.
Help... me...
What's he saying?
Some bastard hammered his balls.
What?
That's insane!
Who broke your balls?
Who are you?
What the hell!
The buses have stopped running.
Where are you headed?
Pardon me?
Where are you going?
To Sung-min Apartments.
Sung-min?
Well. it's kind of on the way.
Hop in.
I'll give you a ride.
It's okay. but thanks.
I'll give you a ride. Get in.
No. really. It's okay.
It's just down the road.
Hop in.
It's fine.
You sure it's on your way?
Don't worry. Get in.
What?
Huh? Nothing.
Is this a school van?
Ah... shit.
Where did I put it?
Why?
Huh?
Why do you look
like you stepped in shit?
Never seen a thing like this?
Who's there?
Why do you need this
for the insurance money?
I have to identify
the policy holder.
There are too many people
with the same name.
These are all old pictures.
Perhaps this one would do.
I'll ask a few more
standard questions.
Do you have additional
contact numbers for him?
I don't.
But his son does.
Sang-won! Sang-won!
Where did he go?
I think it was Yang-pyung
or Chung-pyung...
Can you verify that this person is
the man I'm looking for?
Is this Mr. Jang Kyung-chul?
It's Kyung-chul alright.
But...
Is this a recent picture?
Why does he look so scary?
Insurance. my ass.
He doesn't give a shit
about anyone.
He abandoned his parents
and his son.
Like he would really take out
a family insurance policy?
It doesn't make any sense!
Don't talk like that!
Am I wrong?
No use protecting him.
- Shut up! You old fool!
- You call that a "son"?
Shut up!
Don't get me started!
How can you say that?
If you can't say something nice.
don't say anything!
Fuck!
By the way...
Doesn't the family get the money
if the policy holder dies?
Are you Sang-won?
Do you know
where your dad lives?
Shit!
Why?
She's a really good singer.
- Maybe I can go.
- Of course you'll go.
My mom is gonna kill me.
Go straight home. girls. Okay?
Yes. ma'am.
Please drive them straight home.
Of course.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Shit.
- Can I help you?
- Is Jang Kyung-chul here?
- Why? Is there a problem?
- We're the police. Where is he?
He's driving the kids home.
Shit. Call his cell phone. now!
Hurry!
LEARNING CENTER
Shit.
Do not cry on me.
Do not cry like a baby.
Let's see.
You have fair skin.
It's okay.
It'll be over quick.
I lost my damn job.
Looks like things are fucked up.
But...
Shit!
Who says I can't like you?
What's wrong with that?
I can like you if I want.
Damn bitches in the world
are always against me.
I can! Can't I?
Shit.
It'll be over quickly.
I'll make it quick for you.
Jang Kyung-chul.
What?
You're alone?
Are you a cop?
Must be right.
The cops found me this quick?
You're shitting me.
Guess you don't know
who you're dealing with.
Damn cops.
What do you expect...
Anyway...
You son of a bitch!
Bastard !
What the hell?
The bastard's a complete psycho.
Shit!
Oh. fuck...
Don't know where you're headed.
but you can hop in.
You don't want a ride?
There won't be other cars.
Why are you
all the way out here alone?
You're pretty lucky. Mister.
Catching a cab out here.
It's on the way
for the man in the back.
You don't mind. right?
Of course not.
It must have been hard
to get a cab here.
Cars hardly ever go by here.
I don't come here much.
Just for work.
You're really lucky. Mister.
Did you hear?
Strange things have been
happening around here.
So there aren't
any passengers out at nights.
But I have two tonight.
Looks like I'm lucky. too.
Right. Mister?
Way out here
in the dark night.
What. Mister?
What's so funny?
Mister?
Yes?
You said we're all lucky. right?
Yeah. I did.
So?
The way I see it...
I think you're damn unlucky.
Crazy bastards.
You're young.
it'll heal fast.
And soccer...
Don't play so rough
that you break your wrists. okay?
Who plays soccer with
their wrists anyway?
Go easy. son. Got it?
Get going now.
Hey. shithead.
I am not your son!
Shit.
Watch the way you talk!
Take off your glasses!
Take them off!
Shit!
Come here. you!
Come here!
Excuse me?
Please come and get
your prescription.
Damn old folks always
talking down to people!
I'll rip your mouth off!
Watch yourself.
How old are you?
Twenty-two.
Nice and young.
Got a boyfriend?
Excuse me?
Bet you have many. huh?
Ah... no. I don't.
You fucking playing with me?
A pretty girl like you
without a boyfriend?
You don't know how to do it?
Excuse me?
If you don't. you don't.
Actually...
I was about to have
a good time last night.
But some bastard
came and ruined everything.
So...
Let's make this easy.
Take it off.
What?
Strip.
Try and enjoy it.
So. take it off.
Strip before I cut up
your face. bitch!
Strip now. bitch!
That's it.
Take off your bra.
Hurry.
Please...
Good.
Take off your skirt.
You son of a bitch!
Who the fuck are you?
You bastard!
Wait!
Stay here.
He'll need to be treated.
Don't act so weak.
This is just the beginning.
Remember...
Your nightmare's
only getting worse.
Close your eyes. Miss!
Look away and
plug your ears.
Son of a bitch!
Damn motherfucker!
You want to die?
You want to fight me. huh?
Damn son of a bitch!
Motherfucker.
Fine! Let's see who's the bitch here!
You bastard!
What happened. sir?
Did you have an accident?
His car must have stalled.
Damn dogs.
Always going wild...
At the smell of blood.
Yes. sir.
Is everything okay?
Just worried that's all.
The police think
I'm chasing after Jang.
The cops are after him
themselves as well.
I was thinking...
How about dropping it now?
- Sir...
- You've done enough.
I want you to stop.
But. sir...
Forget it.
Talk to you later.
It's me. Se-yeon.
- Soo-hyun.
- Hi. how are you?
Good.
How are you?
Well. just busy
working on something.
Really?
What kind of work?
You know what I do.
I'm asking about
what we don't know.
Dad gave you
the police files. right?
Soo-hyun?
I know how you feel.
but I hope you'll stop.
It won't bring her back.
Whatever you do to punish him.
things won't change.
Revenge is for movies.
That bastard's a psycho.
Sorry. I have nothing
to say to you.
How come?
We're practically family.
You know how I am
these days?
I keep looking back.
thinking I'm being followed.
And you have nothing to say?
So. please.
This is pointless.
Please drop it.
Sorry. I would better go.
And this is not pointless.
Soo-hyun!
Water!
Get me water!
Aren't you sick of it?
Try it.
You can't get sick of it.
Once you taste this.
you can't eat any other meat.
Crazy bastard.
What did you just say?
Why you little...
Gone insane from
eating human flesh?
Wake up!
I'm Jang Kyung-chul!
Yeah.
I must be damn crazy.
This meat's so good.
I lost my mind.
Why do I cry when I get tense?
Crazy bastard.
Remember when we first met?
Trying to form a militant group
to fuck over the world!
Those were the days.
We weren't afraid of anything!
Cut the bullshit
and give me a cigarette.
Bet he's a family member
of a bitch you killed.
If not. he's some total maniac.
He's our kind.
He's enjoying the excitement
of the hunt.
Catching and letting go
of the prey.
He's playing the hunter.
He relishes torturing his prey.
Man...
I think you're screwed this time.
The bastard must have gone crazy
after losing his bitch.
You've created a monster.
How interesting.
Get some sleep.
We've got plenty of rooms.
You can sleep anywhere.
I'll go prep my next meal.
Damn bastards.
He's enjoying the excitement
of the hunt.
Catching and letting go
of the prey.
He relishes torturing his prey.
He's playing the hunter.
Your nightmare 's
only getting worse.
Amusing...
Now...
I used up all the guts?
Not here. either?
Then...
Shit.
Come on.
Didn't you see your sister?
If you fight it.
it'll be more painful.
I'll end it quickly for you.
So why be suspicious of us?
We didn't ask for money
or the house!
Couldn't let us in. huh?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry!
Should have apologized
a long time ago.
Damn bitches.
Always acting up
when it's too late.
Wait.
Hands. feet.
then head. was it?
Close your eyes.
Better not to look.
Where the hell?
How did you come in
without making a sound?
I'm... pregnant.
I was wondering about you.
You don't look like a monster.
Sick bastard.
Hands. feet. then head.
Right?
Just like you did.
Nothing more. nothing less.
You sick psychos!
Son of a bitch.
Why? Why? Why?
Why. why...
Why...
I'm actually relieved.
You had me worried sick
about you.
It's secret agent
Kim Soo-hyun. right?
Want me to show you
what he's been up to?
Make him stop.
He can't become a monster
to fight the monster.
You know that's wrong.
Where is he now?
Your wounds are treated.
You'll be okay.
You and that bastard
were out for two days.
What happened?
Sir?
Hand the bastard over.
I'm far from done.
What are you going to do?
You know...
It feels like a huge rock is
pressing down on my chest.
Big and heavy.
I promised Ju-yeon that
I would make him feel the same pain.
It's not over.
Far from it.
Okay. no more questions.
By the way.
how's the capsule working?
Unless he has diarrhea...
Don't worry.
The bastard's completely out.
He'll be out
for another day at least.
Sir?
You've changed a lot.
you know?
Hello.
Pain killers. please.
With dexibuprofen.
Dexi what. sir?
- Just give me the strongest kind.
- Sure.
Where are you?
Guess you aren't around.
Are you listening?
Of course you are.
It's been a blast.
Totally unexpected fun.
You!
Want me to guess
who you are?
Your bitch was Ju-yeon?
From Yeon-hee-dong. right?
You hear me?
But. you made a mistake.
You took me for granted.
You'll regret not killing me.
I'll get you soon.
Hello. there.
Wait.
I'll show you what real pain is!
What are you doing!
Hey. you!
By the way...
Before she died. she said...
That she was pregnant.
Begged for her life.
Did you know?
Go! Go! Get here quick!
Or the man I left inside is dead!
Should keep close range
when hunting me.
What the hell!
Where have you gone?
Do we have to do all this
to save bastards like them?
Seeing scum like them
makes me sorry to be human.
Call me when they wake up.
What is it this time?
Yeah. What is it?
What?
Are you sure?
Okay.
Hey.
Jang Kyung-chul is
turning himself in.
You made a damn mistake fool!
Wake up.
I have a question.
Where might our friend be?
You ticked off the wrong guy.
He always gets even.
Know what that means?
First your girl. then her family.
Then he'll give himself up
to the cops.
But...
Your woman didn't have it
all that bad.
Unlike me. Jang likes to give
pleasure before pain.
He gives pleasure first.
Get it?
Funny?
That's funny?
You think it's funny?
I'll give you
a permanent smiley face!
I traced Jang's call.
I was tapping the cops
investigating Jang.
Jang just called them.
Said he'll turn himself in today.
He says he's doing something first.
What if he fucks up again?
Where's he located?
Yeon-hee-dong.
Parcel delivery!
Is this Captain Oh?
I'm Kim Soo-hyun.
What?
What the hell have you done?
If something happens to him.
I'll kill you!
Got that. you bastard?
Send the closest men
to the Chief's house now!
Turn the car around!
Not much resemblance.
Ju-yeon must have taken after
her mom.
Good thing
she doesn't look like you.
Why did you come at me like that?
Old bastard!
You crazy? Huh?
Wait a minute.
Where did I put it?
What should I do
to make that bastard flip?
Will this do the trick?
Like this?
And this! And this!
Like this? Fuck.
Dad?
I'm home.
- What's going on?
- Stay back.
Back away. please!
- What happened?
You can't come in. sir.
Who the hell?
What is it? Step aside.
You're Kim Soo-hyun?
You stupid son of a bitch!
You know what you did?
How dare you come here!
Damn piece of shit.
Back off. Let go!
Damn son of a bitch.
Step aside. Move!
Hello?
Jang Kyung-chul here.
You bastard!
Where the hell are you?
You didn't hurt Se-yeon
did you?
You'll find out later.
What?
Take this.
Hello?
So?
How does it feel?
You shouldn't have fucked with me!
You piece of shit!
Who do you think won?
You think you won?
Or me?
Jang Kyung-chul!
Sir! it's Jang!
Wait! Not now!
Search the car!
What's that car?
What the hell!
Stop that car!
Stop it now!
Get him!
Catch him!
Okay. you're right.
I made a mistake.
I underestimated you.
I'll treat you right
from now on.
You son of a bitch!
What the hell are you doing?
Come on.
I'm just getting started.
Kill me!
You son of a bitch!
Kill me. now!
Hurry up and kill me!
You bastard!
Kill me now!
Not yet.
It won't be long.
If it was that easy.
I would've killed you already.
I'll kill you at your most
painful moment.
When you most tremble
in pain and fear.
I'll kill you then!
Because only that
will be real revenge.
True revenge.
Let me live. Please?
Don't kill me.
Please...
Heard that many times. haven't you?
People begging for their lives.
You enjoyed that. huh?
Don't kill me. please.
I'll pay for my sins.
So...
Let me go. please.
Haven't you done enough?
Please. don't kill me.
I'm so sorry.
I beg you.
Are you scared?
Say it.
You're scared?
Do you realize now
what you've done?
Stop fucking around with me!
You son of a bitch!
Hey.
Cut the bullshit.
You already lost.
You think you got to me?
Huh?
Fuck you.
I don't know what pain is.
Fear?
Don't know that. either.
There's nothing
you can get from me.
So...
You already lost.
Got that?
I hope...
That you suffer even after you die.
Son of a bitch!
You hear me?
You shit! It isn't over.
I'll live no matter what!
You hear me. shithead?
I'm not scared!
You think you can fuck with me?
Dad?
Hey!
Don't open the door!
Dad?
Sang-won!
Don't come in!
What the hell is he saying?
Don't open it!
It's stuck.
No! Why the hell
are the old folks here?
- Kyung-chul!
- Mom!
- Are you in there?
- No. Mom!
Don't open the door!
Shit! Get away!
Kyung-chul!
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm